

const quiz = [
    {
        question: "Why did Johnny orignally purchase the town of Schitt's Creek?",
        choice: ["As a joke for Alexis", "As another location for Rose video", "As a wedding gift to Moria", "As a joke for David"],
        answer: 3,
        photo:
    }
    {
        question: "What does the sign that Roland adds to the town sign say?",
        choice: ["Horace Schitt welcomes you home", "It's not polite to stare!", "Don't worry, it's his sister", "Don't worry, we're family"],
        answer: 2,
        photo:
    }
    {
        question: "What does the type on Alexis' Elmdale college diploma say?",
        choice: ["Alex Rose", "Alexis Rosé", "Pubic relations", "Public Relationships"],
        answer: 2,
        photo:
    }
    {
        question: "What does Moira say was handed down to the women in her family as emergency currency incase they need to leave their husbands in the night?",
        choice: ["A brown crocodile handbag", "An enchilada recipe", "The address of a cobin in the woods", "A suitcase filled with American Dollars"],
        answer: 0,
        photo:
    }
    {
        question: "What illegal business does Johnny try to start in Season 2?",
        choice: ["Raising tigers", "A casino", "Selling raw milk", "Selling counterfit bags"],
        answer: 2,
        photo:
    }
    {
        question: "Which celebrity did Alexis say she used to text for a booty call?",
        choice: ["Ryan Reynolds", "Leo DiCaprio", "Brad Pitt", "Zac Efron"],
        answer: 3,
        photo:
    }
    {
        question: "Who said, "/"I could not be more at one with nature. I do Coachella every year"?",
        choice: ["Alexis", "Moria", "David", "Johnny"],
        answer: 2,
        photo:
    }
    {
        question: "Complete the quote: "/"I do drink red wine, but I also drink white wine. And I've been known to sample the occasional Rosé. And a couple summers back, I tried a ____ that used to be a Chardonnay, which got a bit complicated. I like the wine, not the label.",
        choice: ["Cabernet", "Merlot", "Pinot Noir", "Malbec"],
        answer: 1,
        photo:
    }
    {
        question: "Complete the quote: "/"I once planned Megan Fox's bachelorette on this tiny island off the coast of ____ where nothing is illegal. Like, nothing.",
        choice: ["Romania", "Sierra Leone", "Madagascar", "Montenegro"]
        answer: 3,
        photo:
    }
    {
        question: "For the most part, Alexis has a teasing relationship with her brother. What has become her signature line when talking to him?",
        choice: ["Ew, David!", "As if!", "David, what are you doing?", "Schwing"],
        answer: 0,
        photo:
    }
]